ADE FITRI MAULINA

Bogor, Indonesia | +62 81564750242 | adefitrim@gmail.com | Linkedin: Ade Fitri Maulina | Portfolio

SUMMARY

I graduated from IAIN Syekh Nurjati with a bachelor's degree in Sharia Economic Law. I had good computer skills and was familiar with a variety of administration software during my time in college. In addition to my academic background, I have administrative and marketing expertise, so I am accustomed to maintaining inspection records and document archiving, which are abilities required to become an administrator.

WORK EXPERIENCES

PT OUSEAN GLOBAL DIGITAL – Tangerang Selatan, Indonesia

Feb 2023 - May 2023

Sales Admin | Internship

- Conduct market research internally and externally 3 times per month
- Conduct soft selling sales strategies on potential social media (Facebook, Telegram, and Instagram)
- Conduct email blasting with Mailchimp tools
- Analyze the market competition for One Step Abroad products.
- Create One Step Abroad product content captions 3 times every week
- Successfully collected the One Step abroad product customer database of 45 customers

PT. ATRAHDIS IDEA NUSANTARA - Depok, Indonesia

Feb 2023 - May 2023

Social Media Admin | Internship

- Posted relevant content to 7 Facebook groups, targeting the right audience and driving engagement.
- Created 4 captivating feed captions per week, aligning with the brand and capturing users' attention.
- Regularly analyzed content insights to understand user trends and optimize strategies.
- Actively communicated with social media audience, fostering positive relationships and ensuring prompt responses.

JAVA MULTI MANDIRI - Purwokerto, Indonesia

Feb 2023 - May 2023

Social Media Admin | Internship

- Strategically curated and posted 3 captivating content pieces per week, fueling brand visibility and enticing audiences.
- Masterfully crafted 4 captivating feed captions weekly, capturing users' attention and delivering impactful brand messaging.
- Analyzed insights like a detective, conducting weekly content evaluations to optimize strategies and drive engagement to new heights.
- Cultivated an engaged online community through active and meaningful interactions, fostering brand loyalty and connection.

SKYTREE DGTL - Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2023 - May 2023

Project Management Support | Internship

- Reached out to 848 companies, 65 startups, and 43 universities through email and Instagram DMs within a 3-day period for partnership opportunities.
- Conducted thorough email blast checks using Sheets and Mailchimp to ensure effective communication.
- Boosted daily social media posts, averaging 3 per day, to increase engagement and brand visibility.
- Actively searched and secured 5 event content and media partnerships per week.

METADERMA – Tangerang Selatan, Indonesia

Jan 2023 - April 2023

Administration and Operation Support | Internship

- Oversee administration and ongoing tasks include managing calendars, responding to incoming emails and letters, and keeping track of spending.
- Coordinate internal events and activities such team meetings, presentations, and training.
- Help the operations staff with routine activities including inventory control, product shipping, and shipping preparations.
- Managing administrative duties and customer service-related operations, such as dealing with customer questions, product returns, and support requests.

PENGADILAN AGAMA SUMBER KELAS 1A – Cirebon, Indonesia

Secretarial | Internship

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

• Filing incoming and outgoing letters during activities at the Pengadilan agama for one month

 Filing summons for the parties involved in the trial at the Religious Court to ensure that cases are settled quickly

Registrar | Internship Sep 2022 – Oct 2022

- Create as many as 50 divorce certificates each day
- Create a test schedule for a week's worth of activities.
- Enter court information on the Sistem Informasi Penelusuran Perkara (SIPP) website once a day for 100–200 cases.

DPRD KABUPATEN CIREBON – Cirebon, Indonesia

Finance Departement | Internship

Feb 2022 - Mar 2022

- Recap the finances used in DPRD activities in single day
- Carry out the preparation of implementation and administratice services in field of planning and budgeting
- Receiving and checking accountability letters (SPJ)

Judiciary and Legislation | Internship

Feb 2022 - Mar 2022

- Prepare minutes of the results of Pansus
- Committeee meetings Organize the course of routine and monthly meetings
- · Archive statutory files

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

HIMAHES - Cirebon, Indonesia

Secretary of Ospek Departement

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

- Make an activity proposal for the departement's OSPEK with Ms. Word tools
- Determine the general concept of the event committee
- Create incoming and outgoing letters needed during the activity, be it invitations or activity participants
- Create minutes of regular meetings with Google docs tools
- Creating meeting schedule and activity timelines with Google sheets tools
- Leading a routine meeting of the department's OSPEK activities
- Collecting database of new student major

Event Division Coordation

Jan 2021- Aug 2021

- Solving an unexpected problem in an activity and leading the event
- Create a rundown and timeline of activities
- Direct the committee to carry out their duties appropriately and quickly

Departement of Education

Dec 2021 - Aug 2022

- Successfully created a essay (KTI) and article writing routine with 30 members
- Organize seminars for students or the general public that are held online or offline organize training that can guide students to be more active
- Collecting database of students who are potential for eduacational activities into excel tools

COURSE & CERTIFICATION

<u>Data Science</u> **by** ASEAN Data Science Explorer <u>Microsoft Excel Basic to Advanced</u> **by** My Skill <u>Admin Program Profesi</u> **by** Pintarnya.com May 2023 May 2023 April 2023

EDUCATION

IAIN Syekh Nurjati Cirebon – Cirebon, Indonesia 2023Bachelor Degree of Sharia Economic Law (3.74/4.00)

Aug 2019 – Feb

ADDITIONAL

Technical: Microsoft Office, Microsoft Power Point, Microsoft Excel, Google Sheets, Google Docs

Languages: Native Proficiency in Indonesian, Professional Work Proficiency in English

Skills: Public Speaking, Relationship, Continuous Learning, Problem Solving, Marketing, Adminitration,

Copywriting